these days staying healthier seems
harder than ever but FRU to the most
basic health advice seems impossible
which brings us to tonight's big
question what the people want from me
from me first we need to get enough
exercise in general adults should get
about five hours a week of moderate
exercise or two-and-a-half hours or more
of intense activity or some combination
of the two it's crazy that humans have
to make time to exercise we have to go
to a room and lift heavy things just to
be healthy you know who didn't have to
have time for exercise cavemen cuz they
were too busy staying alive they didn't
need to spend an hour walking upstairs
that never went anywhere they they were
just busy spending that all their day
running away from a saber-toothed tiger
that's why every week I set a tiger free
in the park just to help others but fine
let's say you find a few hours a week to
exercise what else ages 18 to 64 regular
sleep seven to nine hours is recommended
why
seven to nine hours just sleeping sleep
sucks it's when bad things happen people
die suddenly you can oversleep and lose
your job no one's ever caused an
accident by falling awake at the wheel
plus nighttime night times when the
ghosts come out and stand at the foot of
your bed what's in your sleep hey guys
why are you watching me sleep instead of
hoarding a woman's locker room at the
equinox gym you're an guys you
ghost oh I hope you die die more
[Laughter]
[Applause]
but it's not just enough to get your
impossible 7 to 9 hours consistent and
regular sleep health patterns are
important where you're going to bed and
waking up at the same time where you
have a cool quiet dark room putting your
devices away you're not drinking
caffeine or alcohol right before bed and
you're exercising on a daily basis who
can do that nobody goes to bed the same
time every night what if you're out with
friends what if you're in a baseball
game and it runs into extra innings or
you have to bury a corpse and then you
go back to your car and you realize that
you've accidentally buried your key in
the holes or you go back and you dig out
the key and then you get the key and you
get back in the car and now you've
already lost a couple hours sleep so
you're tired you're fall asleep of the
wheel and you hit a skateboarding kid
kind of looks like a runaway no one will
miss him should I bury him yeah it
probably should say you bury the kid and
then you get back to your car either and
key thing again saying it and then by
the time you get home you'd only got
about three hours sleep and you can't
sleep because there's a scape wood ghost
at the end of your bed
[Music]
by far the hardest part is staying
healthy is eating right and for most of
us the damage is already done thanks to
the good old fashioned us food pyramid
the wide bottom of the pyramid gave many
the impression that eating a diet with
lots of carbs was good but decades later
the fallout from the food pyramid may
have accidentally made our diets less
healthy and quite possibly made the
obesity and diabetes problem even worse
it was a triangle where the biggest
widest bit at the bottom was full of
plaster and bread if you eat that
pyramid your body will look like that
pyramid and and we we hung this up at
schools and we were all taught the old
saying and Alfredo say what your day
keeps the doctor away
oh the chest pains mean it's working now
in all fairness is better than a food
pyramid from the 1950s where level 2 is
justice pestis and cigarettes but now we
know that everyone should eat more fruit
and vegetables and and what is more
actually mean because research says I
need 10 servings of fruit every day and
that just seems like way too much and
fruit note to self look up how many
servings of juniper berries are in a
whole thing of Gen I hope instead
there just aren't enough hours in the
day I can't sleep and work out and eat
an entire bowl edible arrangement and
drink eight glasses of water each day
and still have enough protein and
vitamins and antioxidants and probiotics
and good fats and I need satisfaction
for my full-time job I also need to
spend time with families and friends but
I can't text them or call them because
screen time is bad and of course I need
time for self-care like meditation and
whatnot plus I have to wait three times
a week to stop prostate cancer actually
that that one's pretty easy we have
three commercial breaks during this shot
so what do people want from me I'm doing
my best to be healthy but it's only
stressing me out we may be more stressed
than you want to be and it really has
bad repercussions on your health it's
linked to all six leading causes of
death we'll be right back
[Music]